Princess Mirika, please calm down.
Well, it is her first date
outside the castle.
I guess I can't blame her.
Master Gurion has arrived.
Thank you.
Your Highness.
Yes, Laura?
Why is she putting on airs?
Master Kunon Gurion has arriv—
Oh, Your Highness!
Good evening.
The moon is beautiful tonight.
I can't see it, but I hope it's true.
Since it is our first night out.
Oh, Kunon!
I was the princess at school,
but I will escort you today.
Princess, your hand?
Yes.
So that's Master Kunon Gurion.
KUNON THE SORCERER CAN SEE
QUITE A BOY AND A NEW MASTER
Welcome to my restaurant, Master Gurion.
Here's to the beautiful blue
of your eyes and your dress.
Gentlemanly poise and behavior.
No wonder he stole
Princess Mirika's heart.
So you visited the Black Tower today?
Yes. Starting with your
big sister, Lady Raysha,
every one of them was impressive.
The magical power of Grand
Master Blue Cheese especially
was just like your full coiffure.
My goodness.
Is that the right metaphor?
I passed the test as well.
I haven't heard who my
magic teacher will be,
but I'm sure they'll arrange it nicely,
just like your sharp nails with
beautiful colors and shapes.
I've listened to so many
interesting stories.
Oh. Of course your stories,
which sparkle like bird-repelling charms
swinging in the wind on a wheat field,
are more engaging.
Hm. This meat is quite refreshing!
What exactly is "refreshing meat"?
He is a bit strange,
but Princess Mirika looks happy.
Your Highness.
Yes?
Right now, a dinner like
this is the best I can do.
But when we get married, we'll spend
time together like this every day.
I can't wait for the future where
I'll be walking by your side to come.
I take back what I said!
Kunon Gurion... He's quite a boy.
Me, too!
Your Highness, you need
to go to bed already.
Master Kunon!
Could I ask for your help?
A-rubu.
This is it!
This gets the dirt off really well.
I was in the middle of writing a report.
This won't do, Master Kunon.
You've been shutting yourself in your
room since you returned from the castle.
I want to write it down before I forget.
Going outside and spending
time in the sun
is one of your important jobs as
a child. It can affect your growth.
So women prefer tall men, after all?
Some do, indeed.
But I like you, Master Kunon,
whether you're tall or short.
Thank you.
I also like...
Oops, I shouldn't say that, since I don't
want to be rude to Princess Mirika.
Oh, that's not fair!
You're such a ladies' man
for making me say it!
By the way, did a letter ever come for me?
No, sir.
So they haven't decided yet.
Decided what?
My teacher.
Sir!
Sir?
I'd rather not go...
I hope I can come back safely.
Mr. Zeon?
Whoa!
Ugh...
Victo. Don't you dare interfere
with my precious sleeping time.
This is why I didn't want to come.
I didn't ask you to come.
The Grand Master is calling for you!
The old-timer is?
Yes!
Iko, my new teacher has been assigned!
That's great.
Who is it?
Um, Ze-oh-n-ly...
Zeonly Finroll.
The person Brother and
Mother were talking about!
The Master Zeonly, who is rumored to
be a magnificently gorgeous sorcerer?
You know him, too?
Of course, I do!
Every woman in Hughlia knows him!
What do I do, what do I do?!
I need to ask for a new maid
outfit from your father!
I have to put on makeup!
What do I do, what do I do?!
Showing my beautiful
Iko to some other man?
Jealousy will drive me crazy—
Sorry, Master Kunon.
I don't have time for that now!
Oh no, I need to do my nails!
And my hair, too!
And lose weight!
Oh.
I'm sorry to ask you this all of a sudden,
but I guess I don't need to apologize?
No, Sister Raysha.
Inconvenient, isn't it?
A Royal Sorcerer must have a direct
order from royalty to go outside.
Guarding me should be a
good enough reason, right?
Yes. Anyhow...
Why did that man get chosen?!
I wanted to be Kunon's teacher, too!
Sister Everille, Sister Lydalia...
Oh, who was this again?
I hear your fiancé has
an impressive reputation.
Your fiancé only.
Yes. He's an excellent sorcerer,
but that has nothing to do with you two.
Out of the way.
Don't get cocky, Second Princess.
You were reprimanded by
the knight three times.
Why do you know that?
Never mind them.
Right. Thank you very much.
Oh, jeez!
Again, why did that man get chosen?!
I wonder what my teacher is like.
Kunon!
Your Highness?
Did I surprise you?
Yes. I mentally prepare
myself every time I see you.
Seeing you unexpectedly,
I'm lost for words from being nervous
since you're too adorable and beautiful.
Like a frog that's being
stared down by a snake.
But I can't see, so I don't know
what it's like to be stared down.
That brat, huh?
Oh? Did you change your perfume?
It feels mature and it's lovely.
They tell me I'm too young for perfume,
so I don't have any on.
I did change my soap.
That must be it.
It has a mature yet floral scent,
so I'm a butterfly drawn
to a flower right now.
So you are Zeonly...
Incredible.
His magical power is so dense.
It's not just dense. It's sticky as well.
It's almost like honey.
A completely different type of magical
power than Grand Master Blue Cheese.
He's more proficient in magic
than any of the Royal Sorcerers
that I met at the castle.
Kunon? Is everything okay?
I want to look up to him as my master.
Please excuse me. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kunon Gurion.
I know it's out of the blue,
but may I call you Teacher Honey?
Uh? Piss off.
Then what shall I call you?
Master Zeonly.
Make sure to add "master."
Listen well. I hate brats.
What a foul mouth! But so hot!
And I didn't accept the position
of your magic teacher.
It's not like I wanted to be here.
You're here because of the
ties of the rigid hierarchy.
That's life, isn't it?
That old-timer Londimonde told me there
was an interesting brat I should meet.
Grand Master Blue Cheese
sent Teacher Honey to me.
Seriously, what's with those names?!
Pardon me.
I'm Dario Sanz, a knight
of the Third Order,
here to guard Her Highness and Zeon.
Oh! Thank you for
everything the other day.
You know him?
Yes. Not that I personally know him,
but I was the frog stared down by
the snake three times with him.
That was my job.
What a strange kid.
By the way, Master Zeonly is the
magnificently gorgeous sorcerer, correct?
That is correct!
He's perfect!
Obviously.
Is that so?
Since I can't see, I don't understand
what's cool, but you must be amazing.
You're kind of making
fun of me, aren't you?
Not at all.
What a strange kid.
So you brought Master Zeonly here for me.
Thank you very much, Your Highness.
Not at all. I wanted to see you, too.
Likewise, my pretty princess.
Hey, stop it.
I'm here too, you know?
Stop flirting and let's have a fun
discussion about magic with me.
Yes!
That face says he wants to
have fun picking on the kid.
And that face looks so gorgeous!
But it's your master he's going to tease.
You know compound spells, right?
Spells are released from a magic
circle drawn with magical power.
Compound spells are created by dividing
and rearranging magic circles.
How many sections can you handle?
I can do... 31 sections.
What?
I can go up to 32, but sometimes I fail.
Not too shabby.
Me, I can go up to fifty.
Fifty sections?! That many?!
How do you...?
What I'd like to know is how you
got past the twenty-section hurdle?
I layered crests.
And you got there on your own?
Yes. And I used a bunch of little tricks.
"Little tricks" apparently gives a bad
impression, so I call them alterations.
Is he for real?
Why you, Mr. Zeon?
I wanted to be his master, too!
You couldn't be bothered to meet
him when he came here. Not fair!
No, not fair! I want him,
I want him, I want him!
It's not like I'm going because I want to.
The old-timer says he's interesting.
He's not just interesting!
An excellent student like him
won't come around too often.
He goes zoom! And then goes bouncy bounce!
What?
I can see why they were so
invested in getting him.
He is an exceptional talent.
All right, show me what you can do.
But show me how to
do fifty sections first!
It's pointless to teach it
to someone who can't do it.
I'm not gonna waste my time.
Prove what you can do and ask
for instruction fair and square
by sucking up to me.
Kunon would never do that.
Master Zeonly, you're so cool.
Please teach me.
I'd love to see how awesome you are.
He totally did it...
And I'd love to see your generosity,
kindness, tenderness,
and that lonesome profile you
show every now and then!
Well, I really can't see any of that.
Sucking up to you isn't a problem if it
means I can learn how to do 50 sections!
Let me suck up to you!
I have many things to say to you,
but first of all, don't call me master.
I haven't acknowledged you yet,
but I'll show you how awesome I am.
My three-star crest of earth.
How amazing!
Try to destroy this wall with magic.
Otherwise, that's it for you.
With magic?
And I hear your water bed is popular.
Show me.
Yes, sir. A-ori.
Let me observe from here.
Try to do your best...
What is this softness?
It's like a pile of down feathers.
It's not just soft.
It's warm and smells so nice.
This is...
He fell asleep?!
You can't help it.
It's so hard, and yet smooth to the touch.
Very simple at first glance,
but the density of magical
power is incredible.
It's strong enough to sustain
the hardness over time.
Magic is a crest.
A crest means a magic circle.
The caster creates various spells by
rearranging different magic circles,
and those magic circles become
the base of each spell.
Compound magic refers to
the number of times the base magic circle
has been divided and reconstructed,
and it's the essence of magic.
This number shows the level
of magic, and alterations.
It's a crystal of compound
magic with over forty sections.
This is amazing. How can one
increase the sections this much?
Kunon.
Your Highness, let's have a chat.
What?!
Are you sure?
Yes. Let's wait until
Master Zeonly wakes up.
Might as well.
But...
Don't worry. I can destroy it in no time.
Did you sleep well?
How long was I asleep for?
About two hours.
I was totally asleep.
Yo, kid. You look awfully comfortable.
Did you give up?
No. Are you ready for me to break it?
Uh? Sure, if you can.
A-rubu.
That's what he used for laundry.
It's a dirt wall, which
becomes extremely fragile
when it absorbs water beyond its capacity.
I could tell right away
because the texture
was very similar to that of the hard bread
meant for breaking teeth.
You got it more or less right except
for the purpose of hard bread.
But why did you use A-rubu?
Your specialty is A-ori, isn't it?
That's because...
I thought this would be easier.
Rather than using force, you saw the
wall as dirt and chose to wash it away.
I see.
There are spells that're compatible
with certain situations and subjects.
A sorcerer's job is to see through it.
You complimented me!
Does that mean I can be your student?
You don't get to decide that!
Kunon Gurion. Starting today,
you are a student of Zeonly Finroll.
You're the luckiest kid in the world,
because I am going to be your master.
That is true.
I found my master, and Princess
Mirika is by my side.
If I wished for any more,
I'd get a divine punishment.
Oh, Kunon...
Hey, stop it.
Just so you know, your master
comes before your fiancée.
What?
Now that you're my student,
there's a ton of things for you to do.
I have a million things to teach you,
and you'll help with my experiments.
But still...
And what will you do, Miss Fiancée?
What?
He's my student now.
He'll improve a whole lot,
and move up in the world.
And soon, women will swarm
around him to fight over him.
You get what I'm saying,
Miss Ninth Princess?
He is right.
Kunon has grown so much to become
a student of a Royal Sorcerer,
but I'm still a princess of low status.
If I don't do something, there's no
future where Kunon and I can be together!
Master! Please don't be
mean to Her Highness.
Kunon.
I'm actually rooting for you.
You say that, but you actually like
being mean to girls, don't you?
Huh?
And you're the type to
realize it too late.
You're the type to be
mean to a girl you like
and have her stolen from under your nose.
You're the difficult, awkward
type who can't be kind to girls!
Awkward, but still cool!
Hey, brat.
Yes, Teacher Honey!
Don't call me that.
Yes, sir!
I have to do something.
I have to change.
NEXT EPISODE:
INCREDIBLE TRAINING AND INCREDIBLE RESULTS
Next episode: "Incredible
Training and Incredible Results."